(Sheldon:)I heard a woman laughing.
(Leonard:)Oh, uh, yeah. I was trying to
see if I could laugh as a woman.
Oh! Well, good job.
Quite convincing.
(Sheldon:)I smell perfume.
(Leonard:)Air freshener.
(Sheldon:)And is that lipstick
on your cheek and neck?
(Leonard:)Rash. That's a bad rash.
(Sheldon:)My sympathies.
I'm no stranger to the crimson
scourge that is dermatitis.
(Sheldon:)Can I interest you
in a topical steroid
(Sheldon:)from my lotion and
unguent collection?
(Leonard:)Uh, yeah, yeah,
that sounds great.
(Sheldon:)Very well. I'm sure
I can find something
(Sheldon:)that will help
you ditch that itch.
(Leonard:)Okay, he's in the
bathroom. Let's go.
(Sheldon:)Do you prefer
ointment or cream?
(Sheldon:)Cream.
(Sheldon:)With or without a numbing agent?
(Raj:)Without.
Really, Leonard?
(Sheldon:)There are no heroes when
it comes to dermatitis.
(Leonard:)Fine. With.
(Sheldon:)Prescription or
non-prescription strength?